It's because that's what you think!
That's why you adopted Rin,
despite killing her father
and your own senior!
Techut's fingerprint is on here.
Hurry and collect it,
so we can enter the lab.
‪-Hey!
‪-Oh no!
Don't let Taiga out of the 3C building.
Why are you so nice to me?
We'll have to kill each other eventually.
So you just invited yourself over?
While you're here,
can I ask you something?
Sure.
So 3C-coins can be used to buy anything,
both legal and illegal stuff, right?
Yeah.
So if we have those coins
in our crypto account, we can buy stuff?
Yes.
The purchases cannot be traced either.
Then they can also be hacked.
What are you trying to do, Aru?
Can you teach me how to trade crypto?
I want to get rich fast.
You'll teach me, right?
Sure,
but there's a risk
in all kinds of investment, Aru.
You have to remember that investment
is the competition between greed and fear,
just like how every coin has two sides.
Or another good metaphor
is how you can use knives to cook,
but at the same time,
you can also use them to kill people.
Get it?
Yeah.
Thank you for rushing here, Mr. Taiga.
I may work spontaneously,
but I never avoid my responsibilities.
If our principles clash,
I'll have to quit this job.
You don't have to.
3C still wants to enter
challenging markets.
You know, I still remember
what we talked about.
Yes,
it takes three things to do marketing.
The brain, the heart, and sex.
The hardest thing to win over
is the heart.
That's why 3C
needs your good ideas, Mr. Taiga.
It's so we can win over people's hearts.
I really appreciate it, Ms. Nun.
I feel like I have a lot of freedom
working for you.
I feel very at ease.
Rin needs to stay here until she recovers.
Once you go back to 3C,
you'll face a lot more problems.
Who knows when we'll even find
the leader of Fire Phoenix.
I need to be there to help you.
It's okay, Khanin.
I can take care of myself.
But…
Rin needs someone to take care of her.
I want to leave Rin…
in the care of the one I trust the most.
I'm only here because of Taiga,
not you.
If Rin wants to quit,
what does she need to do?
Since when did you become Rin's new boss?
I want Rin to work with me.
Have Rin tell me herself.
She won't be able to come for now.
You can go to jail
for false imprisonment, Mr. Taiga.
Actually,
it's more like she's under protection.
Why would she need your protection?
I bet you know why.
This is 3C.
I own this place.
Rin works for me.
Have her contact me herself.
What's she doing? Where is she?
Why would she need your protection?
If she can explain it,
then I'll let her stay
wherever she's supposed to.
This is Rin speaking, Mr. Naruban.
How are you?
I failed in my duties.
I was out of line.
I just up and disappeared.
I'd like to quit.
At least you feel guilty.
I'm sure you have your personal reasons.
You don't have to quit yet.
You may take some time off.
Thank you.
Once you recover,
come and apologize to me in person.
Understood.
You're giving her time off
without telling HR.
Why?
You've never given anyone
this kind of privilege.
Can't I make any changes?
This is not the way I want you to change.
You know I'd never do what you want.
Why?
Is it so hard to do something for me?
It's the last thing I'd do
for an insatiable wife like you.
Cuss me out all you want,
but I really want you to know
that I love you the most.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
So,
you never loved me, did you?
I used to love you,
until I saw you buying
that very rare, limited-edition watch
the day before my birthday.
I thought it'd be a gift from my wife,
but no.
That watch ended up on the wrist
of another man.
The man who had a business deal with 3C.
The man who's Nunnapat's real father.
Well, you never took care of me.
You left me all alone--
No matter how lonely you feel,
you can't cheat on your husband!
I won't stand looking like a cuck
because I'm a lousy husband.
Just let everyone know
you're an evil, good-for-nothing wife
who sleeps around,
but I need to look like
the best husband and father ever.
You're a selfish jerk!
Yes, I am. So what?
You're just one of my assets.
Forget putting on your wings
and flying away to find happiness.
You deserve to die painfully
in this cage, Giranun.
Aru. Rin.
Want some? The locals here gave us this.
Huh?
Wow.
Is it good?
Feel free to chat with your friends,
but make it quick.
It gets cold quickly around here.
You'll recover more slowly.
I'll be around. Call me if you need me.
You know,
he's as aggressive as a dog.
So, who is he?
Khanin, a friend of Taiga's.
How did you two get here?
Sun and I swapped shifts
with our coworkers.
I was worried. I wanted
to see you with my own eyes.
Thank you so much.
I'll go back as soon as possible.
You don't need to.
Stay and recover a little longer.
You look so exhausted,
and who knows if the cure
gave you any side effects.
Everything's still in a trial phase.
Yeah.
Take care of Aru for me.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of her as well as I can.
- Take care, okay?
- Sure.
ARU
My friends already left.
Thank you for letting me see them.
Rin.
Can I ask you something?
Do you know Inspector Phumin?
Hm.
Not really. Why do you ask?
I was just wondering about something.
But if you don't know him, that's okay.
Why'd you stop here?
We need to talk, Aru.
Can we talk at home?
No. We have to talk right here, right now.
If you're gonna act this way,
I'm going home myself.
Sun.
What are you doing?
Aru. Aru!
TECHUT: DON'T FORGET TO SEND ME THE VIDEO
OR YOUR MOM AND SISTER ARE DEAD. GOT IT?
Good. Whoever betrays me
needs to die a slow and painful death.
What are you smiling about?
Did the coin prices go up?
Just use your brain
for shopping and spending money, Mom.
Leave the difficult things to me and Dad.
Your dearest family.
I really like people like you.
A family person. You're malleable.
You know Aru, right?
No, I don't.
If you lie to me,
you'll be seeing a video of my men
killing your mom and sister!
You're an animal!
You're an animal too.
You're my obedient pet.
You will do everything I say.
Got it?
Aru.
It's late. What are you doing out here?
I can't sleep. I miss my friends.
Your friends were just here.
I don't know.
I suddenly miss them.
Maybe I'm too worried about them.
I bet you understand.
I'm sure you have friends too.
I used to, but that was long ago.
- What about now?
- I have none.
- What about your family?
- None. Let me ask you too.
I have friends, as you saw.
And your family?
None. Just like you.
Everyone has a family, though.
Then tell me about yours. I'm waiting.
I had a dad,
a mom, and a younger sister.
They're all dead.
What about you?
I never said
I'd tell you my story in exchange.
That's not fair. Do you not trust me?
Trust cannot be proven by words alone.
I already know you don't trust me,
so no matter what I tell you,
you won't buy it so easily.
You're both still up?
We were just talking.
Ah.
It's kind of pretty here at night too.
Aren't you scared?
Some women are afraid of the dark.
I'm not.
Being out in the light too much
can be dangerous too.
Yes.
Please take care of your health, Ms. Rin.
If you'll excuse me.
Good night.
I'm not sleepy yet.
No worries at all.
Aru won't pick up.
INCOMING CALL - DHAMMATAT - MOBILE
She hasn't picked up
since she left Inseethong Farm.
Sun went with her, didn't he?
Maybe they just want
some alone time together
to talk,
sleep together,
and sleep in together.
Didn't I make you feel fuzzy at all?
We should assume the worst.
Aru isn't obsessed with romance like you.
How do you know that?
I know everything on earth.
It's just that I may or may not tell you.
I'm not talking about information,
but rather feelings.
Feelings. Got it?
Yes.
Aru is here.
That's in Bangkok.
And not her old house either.
Where's that?
I don't know either.
You can hack CCTV cameras, can't you?
Don't be silly.
I'm not that kind of person.
There. I did it.
Whose house is that?
Why'd she go there without telling us?
One hot americano, please.
Here you go.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
Is Aru with Rin right now, Sun?
Or is she with you?
I'll only ask once.
I don't like asking twice.
She's not with me.
Why are you in my office?
This building's got
security cameras everywhere.
If you didn't betray me,
your life would've been better, Aru.
I was going to buy you a house,
and once I get tired of you,
I'd take you to my friend,
so he can have a try too.
It's green!
Profit!
I made a profit!
Long live 3C-Coin!
It's pretty.
Would you like to try it on?
Sure.
Take her.
Please try these on.
Excuse me.
Try walking in it.
Okay.
What do you think?
You look very pretty.
I'll do another experiment
at Uncle Narumit's farm.
You'll be shocked to see
how fast our virus can kill.
Maybe six months, one month,
or instant death.
Hold off on the experiment.
- Dad.
- Listen to me.
If you keep getting people sick or killed,
Indhorn will catch on to you, and the farm
will no longer be safe for you.
Government officials
will storm it to investigate.
Then we can do the experiment
in the basement here.
Hey.
You want us to fall apart
and go to jail or something?
How will we fall apart, Dad?
We're well-connected. All the police
and prosecutors are your people.
Some bodies aren't so easy to hide.
Then don't.
Grind all their flesh and bones.
Dump them in the ocean.
There won't be any DNA left.
I'm ordering you, so do as I say.
Pause the experiment with the people.
People who want to thrive
aren't afraid of silly stuff like this.
If I'd been as reckless as you,
I wouldn't have lived to this day.
Hold off on the experiment. Just wait!
Why are you out here?
I wanted to go for a walk.
Are you all better now?
I'm doing fine.
You're lying. You're not fine.
I promised Taiga
to take care of you for him,
so I have to do it.
Don't force yourself.
Sometimes we have to force ourselves
to do what we don't want to.
I want to kill you,
yet I have to take care of you.
Well, here's your chance.
Don't challenge me, Rin.
I'm only holding back
for Taiga's sake. I feel bad for him.
Throughout Taiga's life,
too many cruel things
have happened to him.
He's been lonely long enough.
He shouldn't have to be betrayed
by someone close to him too.
Rin, Rin!
Sit down.
Why are you bleeding?
I'm fine.
You relapsed, didn't you?
I was bleeding
out of my mouth this morning.
You must be happy I'm nearly dying.
But you won't die so easily.
Can you stay away from Taiga already?
I never held anyone back,
and I don't have to run away from anyone.
Then listen carefully.
Taiga would lose it all
just because he's worried about you,
yet you still don't know
how important your life is to him?
And if he still has to keep
protecting you like this,
he might even die
before finding the person
who killed his family.
And as for you,
you have a goal in mind too, don't you?
That goal of yours
that you won't tell anyone.
I won't look back anymore.
I'll only look forward.
And my life goal is no one's business.
Not yours either.
You can go ahead
and tell Taiga to stay away from me
if you think forcing him
will make you feel better.
- Who?
- Punlop.
He followed you here.
How did he know I'm here?
He's not stupid.
He must've guessed
based on what's related to Naruban.
Go hide.
Sharp nose, you mutt.
What a surprise to see you here.
You're the one who needs to tell me
what you're doing here.
- I'd rather not.
- Tell me what the hell you're doing here!
What about you? Hiding someone?
Ever since you wore your collar
and got a new owner,
you sure bite deep.
Well, at least
I'm not some cop
who threw his honor away in the trash,
who deceives, bends the truth,
and only thinks about his own benefit.
You really should've been dead
long ago, Punlop.
Yet I survived every single time
because I'm smarter than you.
What the hell?
When you die,
no one will cry for a guy like you.
And a guy like you should die already.
Go, go!
Damn you, Punlop!
You need more people here.
This isn't just about Ms. Rin.
You're too lax. At this rate,
anyone can do anything on your farm.
Okay.
I'll have my workers tighten up security
where you and Ms. Rin are staying.
But where's Ms. Rin?
I'm safe.
Uncle Punlop didn't hurt you two, right?
That scumbag just won't die.
If he already got here once,
he won't stop there.
When he suspects something,
he never lets it slide.
Mr. Indhorn,
I shouldn't stay here.
I don't want any more trouble
for your farm.
I can't let you leave my farm
and risk your life either.
Here, you have me and Mr. Khanin.
You'll be safe for sure.
I'm really sorry.
Get better soon.
Once you do, we'll go face Punlop again.
My virus.
The cure and the vaccine
can only be bought by 3C-coins.
You did your job very well.
Rest assured,
your mom and sister will be safe.
Thank you.
I have another job for you.
I'm not killing anyone again.
You won't have to.
And you're a pro at this job.
Find a way to inflate 3C-Coin
so that I profit 100 million in two days.
Then, I'll tell my men
to let your mom and sister go.
Want to know who killed your father?
Don't go. Uncle Punlop will kill you.
I was just thinking about you,
my lovely niece.
Rin!
Help me.
Who did this to you?
Who's your boss, Uncle?
Why ask about Damon out of the blue?
Dad--
Pok, help me! Please help my son.
Where are my brothers?
Where the hell are my brothers?!
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya